Finding Aid for the Joseph Chouinard Papers, 1926-2008
State University of New York at Buffalo. Music Library
Joseph Chouinard Papers, 1926-2008
Mus. Arc. 71.1
Chouinard, Joseph Jerod, 1926-2014
6 boxes (311 folders)
State University of New York at Buffalo. Music Library
The collection contains personal documents, correspondence, concert programs, and clippings that document the life of singer and librarian Joseph Chouinard.
Administrative Information
Terms of Access
Materials can be examined by qualified researchers in the Music Library during hours of operation during which Music Librarians are present. In order to insure access, researchers are advised to contact the Music Library in advance of visits.
Acquisition Information
Gift of Joseph Chouinard, 2006.
Accruals and Additions
No further accruals are expected to this collection.
Biographical Note
Joseph Chouinard was born in Middletown, Connecticut. His birth certificate lists his middle name as Gerard and his date of birth as May 4th, 1926. However, later documentation shows his date of birth to be May 7th, 1926 and his middle name to be Jerod. It is unclear why this discrepancy exists, though it should be noted. He graduated from Middletown High School in 1944. Following graduation Joseph enlisted in the United States Navy. He served in the Navy from 1944-1946, during which time he was stationed in Okinawa, Japan. After he was discharged he attended the University of Connecticut, graduating with a BA in Music in 1950. He stayed at the university and in 1952, obtained his Master of Arts and Music Degree. Later, he obtained his MLS in Music Librarianship from State University of New York College at Geneseo in 1970. In addition to his degrees, Joseph studied with Nadia Boulanger at Fontainebleau in 1957 and 1958. He also attended the 1961 Session of the Summer School for Singers in Oxford, England.
Throughout his life, Joseph performed both nationally and internationally as a bass baritone. He performed both as a chorus member and as a soloist, including performances at the Tanglewood Festival, Calvary Church in New York City, the Tri-Cities Opera Company in Binghamton, the Aspen Music Festival, the Florida International Music Festival, Columbia University, Arundel Opera (Maine), Theatre Under the Stars in Atlanta, Georgia, and with the University Opera Studio at the State University of New York at Buffalo.
His music librarianship career included positions as Music and Art Librarian, California State College at San Bernardino (1971-1974), Music Cataloger, State University of New York at Buffalo (1974-1978), Music Librarian, State University of New York College at Fredonia (1978-1991), and Exchange Music Librarian at Royal Holloway College, Great Britain (1983-1984). After retiring, Joseph Chouinard remained active as a volunteer at the State University of New York at Buffalo Music Library and at the Buffalo Veterans Administration Hospital where he led patients in various arts activities such as readings of plays and poetry. He died in Buffalo on January 6th, 2014.
Scope and Content Note
This collection consists of 309 folders, which range in date from 1926-2008. There is a series of personal papers which contain his birth certificate as well as transcripts and degrees from his various schooling. The correspondence series contains writing from both personal and professional contacts. The writings and collected research series contains newspaper articles and poems by Joseph. It also contains papers mostly written for academic purposes as well as book reviews. The collection contains programs from various concert performances. There are approximately 37 programs for concerts on which Joseph was a performer and approximately 87 programs for concerts on which he did not perform. The series of publicity and promotional materials contains subseries of musical and non-musical items. Lastly, the press clippings series chiefly contains reviews of performances in which Joseph participated.
Arrangement
The collection is arranged in seven series:
I. Personal documents
II. Correspondence
III. Writings and collected research
IV. Concert programs
V. Publicity and promotional materials
VI. Press clippings
Container List
- Personal documents, 1926-2006, I.; Folder 1-12
  Arranged in chronological order.
  - Birth certificate 4 May 1926, 1 item (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Middletown High School Diploma 15 June 1944, 1 item (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - St. James's Church (New London, Conn.) Order of confirmation 1947, 1 item (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - University of Connecticut 1950-1959, 4 items (Box 1, Folder 4)
    Bachelor of Science diploma, 11 June 1950
    Master of Arts diploma, 8 June 1952
    Sixty-ninth annual commencement booklet, 8 June 1952
    Official transcript, 1952 or after
  - Teaching certificates for the state of Connecticut, 1956-1958, 3 items (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Fontainebleau Music School 1957, 2 items (Box 1, Folder 6)
    Certificate of attendance for summer 1957
    Staff contact list
  - California State College San Bernardino 17 March 1970, 1 item (Box 1, Folder 7)
    Invitation for employment.
  - State University of New York College at Geneseo 1970, 2 items (Box 1, Folder 8)
    Master of Library Science diploma, 21 August 1970
    One-hundred and fourth commencement booklet, 24 May 1970
  - State University of New York College at Fredonia 1982-1991, 6 items (Box 1, Folder 9)
    Exchange proposal for Royal Holloway and New Bedford College 1 December 1982
    General courtesy and privileges letter 30 June 1983
    Request for tour of John Rylands University Library of Manchester 15 September 1983
    Letter from supervisor about being in England 9 November 1983
    Reed Library professional activities update form 15 September 1978
    Praise of La Boheme performance by Thomas H. Carpenter, Professor of Music 20 November 1989
    Notice of intention to retire 7 May 1991
  - Royal Holloway and New Bedford College 1982, 3 items (Box 1, Folder 10)
    Letter of exchange proposal from E. Hartt to J. Saulitis at State University of New York College at Fredonia 2 December 1982
    Chapel schedule March 1984
    Library card
  - State University of New York at Buffalo 1973-2006, 5 items (Box 1, Folder 11)
    Letter of recommendation from Richard Saylor 9 August 1973
    Letter of recommendation from Arthur Nelson 9 August 1973
    Letter of recommendation from John Kucaba 10 August 1973
    Joe Chouinard Day in the Music Library (80th Birthday) 9 May 2006
    Printed image to correspond with Joe Chouinard Day 9 May 2006
  - Curriculum vitae 1973-circa 1981>, 1 envelope (Box 1, Folder 12)
    6 August 1973
    circa 1974
    circa 1975
    circa 1981
  - Additional personal documents, 1945-1970, 4 items (Box 1, Folder 12a)
    Contains several personal identification cards, commencement program, and copy of birth certificate.
- Correspondence, 1957-2007, II.; Folder 13-66
  Arranged in alphabetical order by author's surname.
  - [unknown], Bob and Joanne, 1979-08-17, 1 item (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Altshuler, Blanche, 1987-08, 1 item (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - American Church in Paris, 1957-12-16, 1 item (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - American Civic Association, Inc., 1965, 2 items (Box 1, Folder 16)
    1965-05-03
    1965-11-03
  - Banes, Mildred, 1959, 1 item (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Barbara Walters Specials, 1978-10-24, 1 item (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Benvenga, Nancy, 1972-09, 1 item (Box 1, Folder 19)
    Includes copy of article written by N. Benvenga entitled On Loan from the Army.
  - Bibliotheque Nationale (Paris, France), 1971-10-06, 1 item (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Binghamton Public Library, 1967-11-30, 1 item (Box 1, Folder 21)
    Copy of letter to Harold Mason regarding item donated to library by J. Chouinard
  - British Information Services, 1961-03-20, 1 item (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Burgess, Michael (aka Reginald, Robert), 2002-2003, 2 items (Box 1, Folder 23)
    2002-12
    2003-12
  - Carey, Paul, 1975-04-01, 1 item (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Center for Human Development (Jersey City, N.J.), 1981-05-25, 1 item (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Chouinard, Joseph, 1970-1978, 3 items (Box 1, Folder 26)
    1970-10-28
    1972-10-12
    1978-01-16
  - Cooper, Kenneth, 1961-1969, 18 items (Box 1, Folder 27)
    06-04-67 correspondence includes copy of letter of recommendation
    1961-01-13
    1961-12-10
    1962-09-23
    1962-10-31
    1963-01-01
    1963-01-29
    1966-10-10
    1966-10-14
    1966-10-28
    1966-11-28
    1966-12-12
    1967-01-21
    1967-02-08
    1967-02-13
    1967-06-14
    1968-02-26
    1969-02-26
    1969-05-02
  - Department of Veteran Affairs (Buffalo, N.Y.), 2000, undated, 2 items (Box 1, Folder 28)
    2000-07-10
    undated
  - Evangelical Lutheran Church of the Prince of Peace (Binghamton, N.Y.), 1963-08-11, 2 items (Box 1, Folder 29)
    1963-08-14
    1963-11-3
  - Forget, Louise, 1971-1979, 6 items (Box 1, Folder 30)
    1971-09-20
    1972-11-13
    1973-01-24
    1973-04-19
    1979-01-04
    1979-05-23
  - Forst, Judith, 2003-2012, 1 item (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - Germain, Gaston, 1972, 2004, 2 items (Box 1, Folder 32)
    1972
    2004-11-30
  - Gibson, Gerald D., 1974-03-19, 1 item (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - Gilmour's Albums, CBC Radio, 1974-07-08, 1 item (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - Hiley, David (Ann), undated, 1 item (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - Hopkins Center, Dartmouth College, 1965-05-26, 1 item (Box 1, Folder 36)
  - Jauch, David, approximately 1983, 1 item (Box 1, Folder 37)
  - Kent State University, 1972-08-01, 1 item (Box 1, Folder 38)
  - Kenton, Egon F., 1973, undated, 3 items (Box 1, Folder 39)
    1973-01-22
    1973-06-07
  - Kooper, Kees (Mary Louise née Boehm), 1981, 2002-2004, 5 items (Box 1, Folder 40)
    1981-09-22
    2002-12-25
    2004-08-20
    2004-08-23
  - Legg, Arthur Carl, 1970-11-06, 1 item (Box 1, Folder 41)
    Includes promotional flyer for past art show, newspaper clipping and copy of painting.
  - Lucas, James E., 1968-03-08, 1 item (Box 1, Folder 42)
    Includes newspaper clipping.
  - Lucktenberg, George, 1979-02-21, 1 item (Box 1, Folder 43)
  - Maine School (Maine, N.Y.), 1962-02-28, 1 item (Box 1, Folder 44)
  - Mason, Ethelmae, 2004-09-21, 1 item (Box 1, Folder 45)
  - National Audubon Society, 1971-04-21, 1 item (Box 1, Folder 46)
  - Opera Quarterly, 1987-07-06, 1 item (Box 1, Folder 47)
  - Parry, Betty, 1962-1963, 3 items (Box 1, Folder 48)
    1962-01-13
    1962-12-16
    1963-01-15
  - Polish Airlines, 1971-01-13, 1 item (Box 1, Folder 49)
  - Prevet, Carol, 1988-02-11, 1 item (Box 1, Folder 50)
  - Putnam, Tom, 2007-09-26, 1 item (Box 1, Folder 51)
  - Romo, Bob (Cruz-Romo, Gilda), 1977-1984, 2003, 5 items (Box 1, Folder 52)
    1977-08-05
    1978-06-08
    1978-06-20
    1984-11
    2003-12-27
  - Royal Conservatory of Music, 1965, 3 items (Box 1, Folder 53)
    1965-01-9
    1965-03-27
    1965-04-10
  - Royal Holloway College, 1984-1989, 4 items (Box 1, Folder 54)
    1984-01-12
    1984-09-20
    1985-01-09
    1989-10
  - Schlaraffia Bisonia, 1978-12-16, 1 item (Box 1, Folder 55)
  - Sheehy, Matthew, 2002-12-12, 1 item (Box 1, Folder 56)
  - Societe Frederic Chopin, 1971, 4 items (Box 1, Folder 57)
    1971-01-18
    1971-02-03
    1971-03-29
    1971-08-03
  - St. Paul's United Methodist Church (San Bernardino, CA.), 1973-04-1973-05, 2 items (Box 1, Folder 58)
    1973-04-25
    1973-05-14
  - Stanford, Carolyn, 1978-06-30, 2 items (Box 1, Folder 59)
    1978-06-22
    1978-06-30
  - State University of New York at Buffalo, 1974, 1996, undated, 4 items (Box 1, Folder 60)
    1974-04
    1974-05-01
    1996-08-27
  - State University of New York College at Buffalo, 1989-06-16, 1 item (Box 1, Folder 61)
  - State University of New York College at Fredonia, 1984-1987, 2 items (Box 1, Folder 62)
    1984-02-06
    1987-12-15
  - Stetson University, 1967, 3 items (Box 1, Folder 63)
    1967-05-15
    1967-06-09
    1967-06-23
  - Summer School for Singers (Ritchie, Margaret), 1961-1963, undated, 9 items (Box 1, Folder 64)
    1961-03-21
    1961-03-25
    1961-05-16
    1961-06
    1961-07-11
    1961-10-04
    1961-12-29
    1963-01-10
  - Tri-Cities Opera Guild News, 1961, 1 item (Box 1, Folder 65)
  - Whiting, Jim and Julie, 1999-12-02, 1 item (Box 1, Folder 66)
    Includes photograph.
  - Unsorted additional correspondence, undated, 1 folder (Box 1, Folder 66a)
- Writings and collected research, 1954-1995, III.; Folder 67-108
  Arranged in three subseries:
  III.A Articles by Joseph Chouinard
  III.B Writings and research
  III.C Poetry written by Joseph Chouinard
  - Articles written by Joseph Chouinard 1954-1979, III.A; Folder 67
    Arranged in chronological order within the folder.
    - Articles by Joseph Chouinard, 1954-1979, 8 items (Box 2, Folder 67)
      Symphony lauded on visit to Rome, unidentified source, 1954
      Response to opera from Christian Science Monitor, 26 February 1960
      Youngsters intrigued by Dorian Quintet from Sun-Bulletin (Binghamton, New York), 9 April 1962
      Aspen adventure from Valley echo, December 1962
      Letter to the editor from Geneseo Lamron, 7 November 1969
      Festival faculty performs from Meadville Tribune, 18 August 1979
      Faculty soloist featured at final festival concert from Meadville Tribune, 27 August 1979
      Hegyis pleasing in first recital from an unidentified source, approximately 1955
  - Writings and research 1970-1979, III.B; Folder 68-78
    - Program Notes on Benjamin Britten's A Ceremony of Carols for Trinity Episcopal Church (Buffalo, N.Y.), 1978-11, 1 folder (Box 2, Folder 75)
    - Review of: Price, Curtis A. Music in Restoration Theatre with a Catalogue of Instrumental Music in the Plays 1665-1713, 1979-10, 1 folder (Box 2, Folder 76)
    - Book Review for American Reference Books Annual Word-by-word, undated, 1 folder (Box 2, Folder 78)
    - Stream of Consciousness, undated, 1 folder (Box 2, Folder 77)
    - With reference to the Berlioz Romeo & Juliet Symphony, 1970-03, 1 folder (Box 2, Folder 69)
    - Some thoughts on Berlioz, 1970-03, 1 folder (Box 2, Folder 68)
    - Hector Berlioz and Shakespeare; A term paper, 1970-05-16, 1 folder (Box 2, Folder 71)
    - Research for Hector Berlioz and Shakespeare; A term paper, 1970-05-16, 1 folder (Box 2, Folder 70)
    - Notes on Commedia dell'arte, 1975-03, 1 folder (Box 2, Folder 72)
    - Notes on Maruxa by Juan Arnau, translated from Spanish by Joseph J. Chouinard, 1975-07, 1 folder (Box 2, Folder 73)
    - Glyndebourne Festival Programme Books Index Proposal, 1975-09-30, 1 folder (Box 2, Folder 74)
  - Poetry written by Joseph Chouinard 1964-1995, III.C; Folder 79-108
    - Winter's dividend, 1964-01-05, 1 poem (Box 2, Folder 79)
    - Haiku example, 1968-05-16, 1 poem (Box 2, Folder 80)
    - Toss a pillow, throw a ball., 1968-05-17, 1 poem (Box 2, Folder 81)
      Title taken from first line of poem
    - A stare of owls and other stares are eyes of birds just unaware, 1969-11-09, 1 poem (Box 2, Folder 82)
    - Some things go together, 1969-11-09, 1 poem (Box 2, Folder 83)
    - Winter's cemetery, 1969-12, 3 poems (Box 2, Folder 84)
      With: No modern conveniences, In God we trust
    - Homage to Rod Mc., 1969-12-13, 2 poems (Box 2, Folder 85)
      With: Homage to Randell Jarrell
    - Hommage to A. H. Berlioz, 1969-12-18, 1 poem (Box 2, Folder 86)
      Includes Berlioz shadow portrait made of construction paper
    - So smart, so soon yet?, 1970-01-30, 1 poem (Box 2, Folder 87)
    - Slice it, 1970-02, 1 poem (Box 2, Folder 88)
    - Winter, 1970-02-03, 1 poem (Box 2, Folder 89)
    - A rose, 1970-02-10, 1 poem (Box 2, Folder 90)
      Includes copy with corrections
    - Spring, 1970-03-05, 1 poem (Box 2, Folder 91)
    - Awakening spring, 1970-04-12, 1 poem (Box 2, Folder 92)
    - A bat, 1970-05-03, 1 poem (Box 2, Folder 93)
    - It's tough to be a bird, 1970-12-02, 1 poem (Box 2, Folder 94)
      Title taken from first line of poem; Includes newspaper clipped image of a bird
    - Winter's rain, 1970-12-16, 1 poem (Box 2, Folder 95)
    - Visit the colonel, 1971-01-31, 2 poems (Box 2, Folder 96)
      Title taken from first line of poem; Includes newspaper clipped image of Kentucky Fried Chicken bucket with notes
    - There once was a student at Cal-State, 1971-06-03, 1 poem (Box 2, Folder 97)
    - Chouinard, 1972-11, 3 poems (Box 2, Folder 98)
      With: Hungarian song and Today an underdog. Title for Today an underdog taken from first line of poem.
    - The rewards of life, 1973-01-07, 1 poem (Box 2, Folder 99)
    - Conducted to the grave, 1973-01-18, 1 poem (Box 2, Folder 100)
    - A harassed school teacher from Hayes, 1973-03-26, 1 poem (Box 2, Folder 101)
    - A honey bee, unlike a bumble bee can't use its stinger repeatedly, 1976-04-16, 1 poem (Box 2, Folder 102)
    - Graffitti, 1987-04-09, 1 poem (Box 2, Folder 103)
    - Signs of the times, 1993-06-15, 1 poem (Box 2, Folder 104)
    - My name is Irma Pea Greene, 1993-12, 1 poem (Box 2, Folder 105)
    - Piggly wiggly, 1995-12-12, 1 poem (Box 2, Folder 106)
    - I am a thought, undated, 1 poem (Box 2, Folder 107)
    - Moles live in holes, undated, 1 poem (Box 2, Folder 108)
- Concert programs, 1937-2007, IV.; Folder 109-232
  Arranged in two subseries:
  IV.A Programs for performances including Joseph Chouinard
  IV.B Programs collected by Joseph Chouinard
  - Programs for performances including Joseph Chouinard 1948-2002, IV.A; Folder 109-145
    - 1948-11-23, 1 program (Box 2, Folder 109)
      Unknown
    - 1950-03-26, 1 program (Box 2, Folder 110)
      Storrs Congregational Church (Storrs, Conn.)
    - 1951, 3 programs (Box 2, Folder 111)
      1951-05-27 Asylum Hill Congregational (Hartford, Conn.)
      1951-10-03 First Presbyterian Church in Philadelphia
      1951-1952 First Presbyterian Church in Philadelphia Vesper Services
    - 1952, 6 programs (Box 2, Folder 112)
      1952-01-20 First Presbyterian Church in Philadelphia
      1952-02-03 First Presbyterian Church in Philadelphia
      1952-02-10 First Presbyterian Church in Philadelphia
      1952-02-24 First Presbyterian Church in Philadelphia
      circa April 1952 First Presbyterian Church in Philadelphia
      1952-1953 Season Calvary Episcopal Church
    - 1953, 2 programs (Box 2, Folder 113)
      1953-03-09 Calvary Church (New York, N.Y.)
      1953-12-16 Shorter College (Roma, Ga) Progra: contains letter to 'Babe and mom' and sheet music
    - 1954-03-25, 1 program (Box 2, Folder 114)
      St. Peter's (Rome, Ga.)
    - 1955, 6 programs (Box 2, Folder 115)
      1955-04-24 Berry College
      1955-05-01 Berry College
      1955 Season National Music Camp
      1955 Municipal Theater under-the-stars Showboat
      1955 Municipal Theater under-the-stars Call Me Madam
      1955-11 Chattanooga Opera Association Madame Butterfly
    - 1956, 5 programs (Box 2, Folder 116)
      1956 Season Chattanooga Opera Association Rigoletto
      1956 Season National Music Camp Includes listing of camp personnel for 1956 Season and postcard
      1956-07-18 National Music Camp Composers Club
      1956-08-02 National Music Camp University Choir
      1956-08-09 National Music Camp Composers Club
    - 1957, 4 programs (Box 2, Folder 117)
      1957-03-29 Tri-Cities Opera Faust
      1957-07-01 Fontainebleau Schools of Music and Fine Arts Summer Program
      1957-12-15 American Church in Paris
      1957-12-25 Conservatoire Américain
    - 1958, 2 programs (Box 2, Folder 118)
      1958-11-07 Tri-Cities Opera Lucia di Lammermoor Includes promotional poster
      1958-11-30 First Congregational Church (Cromwell, Conn.)
    - 1959, 4 programs (Box 2, Folder 119)
      1959-03-06 Tri-Cities Opera Un Ballo in Maschera
      1959-07-01 Arundel Opera Theatre Annie, Get Your Gun
      1959-10-11 Tri-Cities Opera Madame Butterfly
      1959-12-06 Andrews Memorial Oratorio Choir
    - 1960, 4 programs (Box 2, Folder 120)
      1960 Camp Willoway The Lonesome Train Includes lyrics to Ballad for Americans by Earl Robinson
      1960-07-24 West Presbyterian Church (Binghamton, N.Y.)
      1960-10-14 Tri-Cities Opera Faust Includes promotional poster
      1960-12-04 West Presbyterian Church (Binghamton, N.Y.)
    - 1961, 10 programs (Box 3, Folder 121)
      1961-01-08 West Presbyterian Church (Binghamton, N.Y.)
      1961-01-28 Tri-Cities Opera Workshop The Magic Flute
      1961-04-30 West Presbyterian Church (Binghamton, N.Y.)
      1961-03-10 Tri-Cities Opera Il Tabarro and Suor Angelica
      1961-07-16 West Presbyterian Church (Binghamton, N.Y.)
      1961-07-23 Summer School for Singers, University College Summer Program
      1961-08-05 Summer School for Singers, University College Acis and Galatea and Sleepers Wake
      1961-08-12 Summer School for Singers, University College Die Zauberflöte
      1961-10-14 Tri-Cities Opera La Traviata
      1961-12-03 Hedding Methodist Church (Elmira, N.Y.) includes note to unnamed party
    - 1962, 8 programs (Box 3, Folder 122)
      1962-03-09 Tri-Cities Opera La Boheme Includes promotional poster
      1962-03-14 Columbia-Barnard Festival of the Arts
      1962-05-07 International Singing Contest in Belgium Includes instructions for candidates
      1962-05-25 Tri-Cities Opera Workshop jeremiah
      1962-07 Aspen Music Festival Includes information on vocal repertoire class
      1962-07-27 Aspen Music School Opera Workshop La Contrebasse
      1962-08-10 Aspen Music School Opera Workshop The Pearlfishers Includes newspaper clipping
      1962-08-19 Summer School for Singers, University College Summer Program Includes promotion of 1963 session
      1962-11-04 West Presbyterian Church (Binghamton, N.Y.)
    - 1963-10-27, 1 program (Box 3, Folder 123)
      Lutheran Church of the Prince of Peace (Binghamton, N.Y.)
    - 1964, 2 programs (Box 3, Folder 124)
      1964-03-18 State University of New York at Buffalo The Barber of Seville
      1964-08-02 First Congregational Church (Binghamton, N.Y.)
    - 1965, 3 programs (Box 3, Folder 125)
      1965-07-14 Hopkins Center Summer Program, Dartmouth College
      1965-07-25 Lutheran Chapel of Our Savior (Hanover, N.H.) Includes note to Mom and Babe
      1965-08-21 Hopkins Center Summer Program, Dartmouth College
    - 1967, 4 programs (Box 3, Folder 126)
      1967-01-12 Minor Latham Playhouse Acis and Galatea Includes promotional poster and schedule of Columbia events
      circa July 1967 Florida International Music Festival, An Opera Cabaret A Concert Party
      circa July 1967 Florida International Music Festival The Little Harlinquade and Gallantry
      circa July 1967 Florida International Music Festival La Boheme
    - 1969-02-20, 1 program (Box 3, Folder 127)
      Barnard-Columbia Chamber Chorus Susanna Includes two (2) promotional posters. One with notes on performance and the other with note from Kenneth Cooper
    - 1970-11-29, 1 program (Box 3, Folder 128)
      California State College, San Bernardino
    - 1971-12-12, 1 program (Box 3, Folder 129)
    - 1972-01-30, 1 program (Box 3, Folder 130)
    - 1973-12-16, 1 program (Box 3, Folder 131)
      State University of New York College at Buffalo
    - 1974, 2 programs (Box 3, Folder 132)
      1974-10-26 American Liszt Society Festival
      1974-11-22 State University of New York at Buffalo La Boheme
    - 1978, 2 programs (Box 3, Folder 133)
      1978-07-11 Trinity Church (Buffalo, N.Y.)
      1978-12-24 Trinity Church (Buffalo, N.Y.)
    - 1979, 5 programs (Box 3, Folder 134)
      1979-02-25 Trinity Church (Buffalo, N.Y.)
      1979-02-28 First United Presbyterian Church (Dunkirk, N.Y.)
      1979-08-16 Allegheny Summer Music Festival
      1979-09-30 Trinity Church (Buffalo, N.Y.)
      1979-12-09 Trinity Church (Buffalo, N.Y.)
    - 1980, 2 programs (Box 3, Folder 135)
      1980-01-20 Trinity Church (Buffalo, N.Y.)
      1980-12-21 Trinity Church (Buffalo, N.Y.)
    - 1981, 6 programs (Box 3, Folder 136)